I say "All aboard."
(Sheldon:)You sit quietly and watch.
(Wil:)Can I blow the whistle?
(Sheldon:)You should probably go.
You're going to brush
your teeth on my couch?
No, I'm going to brush
Cinnamon's teeth.
(Howard:)Why bother?
(Howard:)She spends half the time
licking her butt.
(Raj:)And the other half
licking my face.
Thats why I'm brushing her teeth.
(Bernadette:)Hey, guys.
Sorry I'm so late.
(Bernadette:)-Did you already have dinner?
-No, we were waiting for you.
(Bernadette:)That's so sweet.
(Howard:)Yeah. So what do you
feel like making?
(Raj:)Howard, the poor thing
just got home from work.
(Raj:)Let me get you a glass of wine.
(Raj:)I'll cook dinner.
(Bermadette:)-Oh, Raj, you're our guest.
-Don't be silly.
(Sheldon:)Sit.
You look like you've had a long day.
(Howard:)No, she always looks like that.
(Howard:)Because she married an idiot.